Happily ever after begins with a dream.
A Cinderella Story: Christmas Wish is a romance, music,
comedy film directed by Michelle Johnston.
Kat is an aspiring singer-songwriter who dreams of making it big.
However, her dreams are stalled by her reality: a conniving and cruel stepfamily  and a
demoralizing job working as a singing elf at billionaire Terrence Wintergarden’s Santa Land.
Kat Decker, played by Laura Marano.
Nick Wintergarden, played by Gregg Sulkin.
Isla, played by Isabella Gómez.
Deirdra Decker, played by Johannah Newmarch.
Joy Decker, played by Lillian Doucet-Roche.
Grace Decker, played by Chanelle Peloso.
A Cinderella Story: Christmas Wish is a 2019 American musical teen comedy written and
directed by Michelle Johnston and starring Laura Marano and Gregg Sulkin.
It is the fifth installment of the A Cinderella Story film series.
The film was released digitally on October 15,
2019, and DVD on October 29, 2019.
Its stand-alone sequel, A Cinderella Story: Starstruck, was released in 2021.
The film explores themes of musical, christmas, christmas songs, cinderella.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.